<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Koakuma&#39;s Notes</title>
    <link>https://koachan.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Koakuma&#39;s Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<atom:link href="https://koachan.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A New Start</title>
      <link>https://koachan.github.io/post/new-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://koachan.github.io/post/new-start/</guid>
      <description>Update: I finally decided to join the fediverse! It&amp;rsquo;s been fun so far!
Hi, Koakuma here~
Okay so&amp;hellip; this blog started out as a publicly viewable version of my computer- related notes and experiances, especially with less common platforms like PowerPC. As time goes on, I feel like I should write about something better than just random, unorganized stuff.
But there&amp;rsquo;s one problem: I don&amp;rsquo;t know what to write about yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Speck 128/128 Cipher Implementation</title>
      <link>https://koachan.github.io/post/speck-implementation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://koachan.github.io/post/speck-implementation/</guid>
      <description>This is an implementation of the Speck cipher, with 128 bits key and block size, in standard C99 and PowerPC assembly.
Please go to the GitHub page if you want to look at or download the code.
Disclaimer: This is experimental code, use it at your own risk.
General notes I only implement the block core of the cipher. There&amp;rsquo;s no support code for running it in the various modes of operation (other than ECB which is trivial to do).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building dnscrypt-proxy 2 on Debian/ppc</title>
      <link>https://koachan.github.io/post/dnscrypt-debian-ppc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://koachan.github.io/post/dnscrypt-debian-ppc/</guid>
      <description>Update 2019/06/23: I&amp;rsquo;ve moved to unbound now. This page will stay here as a reference but I don&amp;rsquo;t recommend doing this anymore.
A small guide (and note to myself) on how to build version 2 of dnscrypt-proxy on Debian/ppc, since Debian only provides version 1.9.5 in its ppc repositories.
This guide might apply to other flavors of PowerPC Linux too, with some adjustments regarding package installation and file locations.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>